saflii.org 2004-06-06

# SAFLII - About SAFLII: Privacy Policy

SAFLII's privacy policies are based on respect for international standards of information privacy protection. 

## A. Information concerning usage of SAFLII

**A1.** SAFLII collects information which identifies, for each page accessed on SAFLII, the network identity of the machine which has accessed it. SAFLII retains this usage information for purposes of network analysis, usage analysis, and research into usage patterns for the purpose of improving SAFLII services. Access to and use of this information is restricted to SAFLII management and staff, and to researchers working on SAFLII projects and subject to an agreement to adhere to this Privacy Policy.

**A2.** SAFLII does not disclose or publish information which identifies individual machines,or potentially identifying sub-groupings of addresses, without consent. SAFLII does publish aggregated information about usage patterns.

**A3.** SAFLII reserves the right to gather more extensive information that stated above (i) about any attempted access to SAFLII which raise security issues (and, where necessary, to make disclosures to relevent authorities); and (ii) for network analyses on an occasional basis.

## B. Personal information contained in SAFLII databases

**B1.** Some SAFLII databases contain personal information, including the decisions of Courts and Tribunals, and the reports of Royal Commissions. SAFLII publishes these databases with the consent of the public bodies concerned. It is the responsibility of the public bodies which provide these databases to SAFLII to determine, subject to the requirements of the laws under which they operate, the appropriate balance between the privacy interests of individuals and the public interests in dissemination of the information. In particular, if personal data is to be anonymised before publication, this is done by the public body concerned. SAFLII does not and can not censor part or all of the information provided by these public bodies for publication.

**B2.** SAFLII does not consent to the contents of these databases being indexed by other web sites. SAFLII attempts to prevent such indexing occurring by placing these database outside the permitted scope of web 'crawlers', 'robots' or 'spiders' that adhere to the voluntary Robot Exclusion Standard

SAFLII also monitors whether any robots attempt to index these databases in disregard of this Standard, and takes steps to exclude any that do so from any access to SAFLII.

**B3.** SAFLII users should note that there are legal limitations on the use, publication and dissemination of some personal information contained in SAFLII databases. 

**SAFLII reserves the right to exclude access to its databases by users or sites that are in apparent breach of any such legal requirements.**

If you have any comments or suggestions in relation to this policy, please send us some mail.

* * *

**SAFLII:** Copyright Policy **|** Disclaimers **|** Privacy Policy **|** Feedback   
URL: _http://www.saflii.org/saflii/privacy.html_
